const cpquizData = [{
    Question:
        'What is a correct syntax to output "Hello World" in C++ ?',
    Options: [
        'System.out.println("Hello World");',
        'Console.WriteLine("Hello World");',
        'cout << "Hello World";',
        'print("Hello World");',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'C++ is an alias of C#',
    Options: [
        "Don’t know",
        'False',
        'True',
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you insert COMMENTS in C++ code ?',
    Options: [
        '// This is a comment ',
        '# This is a comment',
        '/* This is a comment',
        'None',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?',
    Options: [
        'myString',
        'string',
        'Txt',
        'String',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?',
    Options: [
        'num x = 5    ',
        'double x = 5;',
        'int x = 5;',
        'x = 5;',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?',
    Options: [
        'int x = 2.8;',
        'x = 2.8;',
        'double x = 2.8; ',
        'byte x = 2.8',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to find the length of a string?',
    Options: [
        'getSize()    ',
        'getLength()',
        'length() ',
        'len()',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to add together two values?',
    Options: [
        'The * sign',
        'The & sign',
        'The + sign   ',
        'The / sign ',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.',
    Options: [
        'True    ',
        'False    ',
        "Don’t know",
        'None',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which header file lets us work with input and output objects?',
    Options: [
        '#include <inputstr>  ',
        '#include <iostream>',
        '#include <stream>',
        '#include <iosstring>',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator can be used to compare two values?',
    Options: [
        '<> ',
        '=',
        '><',
        '==    ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'To declare an array in C++, define the variable type with:',
    Options: [
        '{}    ',
        '[]  ',
        '()',
        '<>',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Array indexes start with:',
    Options: [
        '0  ',
        '1',
        "Don’t know",
        'None ',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a function in C++?',
    Options: [
        'functionName()  ',
        'functionName[]',
        'functionName.',
        '(functionName)',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you call a function in C++?',
    Options: [
        'functionName;    ',
        'functionName();  ',
        'functionName[];',
        '(functionName);',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to create a class in C++?',
    Options: [
        'class()  ',
        'MyClass',
        'class    ',
        'className',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?',
    Options: [
        'class myObj = new MyClass();  ',
        'class MyClass = new myObj();',
        'new myObj = MyClass();',
        'MyClass myObj;',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'In C++, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.',
    Options: [
        'NaN',
        'False    ',
        'True   ',
        "Don’t know",],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?',
    Options: [
        'max(x,y)    ',
        'maximum(x,y)',
        'maxNum(x,y)',
        'largest(x,y)',],
    Correct: 0,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which operator is used to multiply numbers?',
    Options: [
        '%  ',
        'x',
        '#',
        '*    ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you create a reference variable of an existing variable?',
    Options: [
        'With the ref word    ',
        'With the & operator',
        'With the REF word',
        'With the * operator',],
    Correct: 1,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing an if statement in C++?',
    Options: [
        'if x > y then:',
        'if x > y:',
        'if (x > y)',
        'None',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'How do you start writing a while loop in C++?',
    Options: [
        'while x > y:   ',
        'while x > y {',
        'while (x > y)   ',
        'x > y while {',],
    Correct: 2,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?',
    Options: [
        'get   ',
        'void',
        'break',
        'return   ',],
    Correct: 3,
}, {
    Question:
        'Which statement is used to stop a loop?',
    Options: [
        'break ',
        'exit',
        'stop',
        'return',],
    Correct: 0,
}]
